#Generated through API from Open Trivia DB
question_data = [
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
}
]
